Curt Stern Papers 1907-1981 Mss.Ms.Coll.5
American Philosophical Society
- Photographs, 1882-1980; 1.0 linear feet items
  - Solzhenitsyn, A.; Timofeef-Ressovsky, S. and Medvedev (seated) - negatives, 2 items (Box 2)
  - Stadler (Box 2)
  - Steinetz, Lotte (Box 2)
  - Stern, Curt (Box 2)
    - Folder 1, ca. 38 items (Box 2)
      - At Conference (Box 2)
      - Bookstore in Mexico selling Spanish ed. of Principles of Human Genetics, Dec. 29, 1965 (Box 2)
      - Busts, 1948; 4 items (Box 2)
      - Charter Day, Mar. 1966 (Box 2)
      - Curt Stern in laboratory at University of Rochester, May 1947; 2 items (Box 2)
      - Curt Stern lecturing: ABO blood groups, Jun. 1959 (Box 2)
      - Curt Stern lecturing: intersexes, Jun. 1959 (Box 2)
      - Curt Stern lecturing: selfsterility, Jun. 1959 (Box 2)
      - Curt Stern working under the microscope at University of Rochester, Jun./Jul. 1930 (Box 2)
      - During classroom discussion, Sep. 1956 (Box 2)
      - Leaning against wall, 1953 (Box 2)
      - "Looking at 'Anlagen,' Corvallis, Ore.", Aug. 30, 1962 (Box 2)
      - Looking in microscope, Aug. 1, 1939 (Box 2)
      - Montreal, 1958 (Box 2)
      - Montreal - picnic, Aug. 1958 (Box 2)
      - N. Truro, Aug. 1940 (Box 2)
      - Negatives, ca. 5 items (Box 2)
      - Oak Ridge, with child, Nov. 6, 1937 (Box 2)
      - Picture in conference brochure, Feb. 14, 1957 (Box 2)
      - Sitting with microscope, Jul. 27, 1954 (Box 2)
      - Standing portrait, 2 items (Box 2)
      - University of Rochester, Feb. 1943; 3 items (Box 2)
      - With Hans Stubbe, Gatersleben, Oct. 10, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Folder 2, 15 items (Box 2)
      - Curt Stern Reading Biology of Drosophila, ca. 1970; 3 items (Box 2)
      - Formal portrait (Box 2)
      - Negatives, 2 items (Box 2)
      - Northwestern University, Home of R. C. King, May 1968; 6 items (Box 2)
      - Small headshots, 2 items (Box 2)
      - With Mrs. Stern (Box 2)
    - Folder 3 - Japan, 1956; ca. 42 items (Box 2)
      - Curt Stern lecturing in Japan, 1956 (Box 2)
  - Stern, Mrs. Curt (Box 2)
  - Steuer, A. in Trieste, 1902 (Box 2)
    (Richard B. Goldschmidt photo.)
  - Strassburger, Eduard (Box 2)
  - Sturtevant, Alfred Henry (Box 2)
    - Alfred Sturtevant with arms akimbo, 1925 (Box 2)
    - "Hot Dog", ca. 1918 (Box 2)
    - Kimber Genetics award, 1957 (Box 2)
    - Lexington, Kentucky, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Negative, 2 items (Box 2)
    - Painting by Frank Johnson, Pasadena, 1945 (Box 2)
    - Rocky Mountain Biological Laboratory, Crested Butte, Colo., Summer 1957 (Box 2)
    - Tarpaulin Cove, Pre 1926 (Box 2)
  - Taylor, J. H. (Box 2)
  - Timofeeff-Ressovsky, N. W., 1943 (Box 2)
  - Toyama, K. (Box 2)
  - Tschermak-Seysenegg, Erich, 1941; 2 folders; 3 items (Box 2)
    - Erich Tschermak-Seysenegg, 1941
  - Uchida, Johru (Box 2)
  - University of British Columbia - Department of Zoology, Oct. 1973; 2 items (Box 2)
  - University of California Berkeley - Staff (Zoology) (Box 2)
  - Waldeyer, Wilhelm; Prof. of Anatomy, Berlin, Oct. 6, 1836 - 1921, 1888 (Box 2)
  - Warburg, Otto: Newspaper and Science cover, Nov. 8, 1931; Nov. 12, 1948; 2 items (Box 2)
  - Weinberg, Wilhelm (Box 2)
  - Weismann, August (Box 2)
  - Wettstein, Fritz von (Box 2)
  - Wilson, E. B., 10 items (Box 2)
    - E. B. Wilson, 1925; 4 items (Box 2)
    - E. B. Wilson reading (frontal view), ca. 1920s; 2 items (Box 2)
    - E. B. Wilson reading (side view), ca. 1920s; 2 items (Box 2)
    - E. B. Wilson with microscope, ca. 1920s; 2 items (Box 2)
  - Witschl, Emil (Box 2)
  - Woodruff (Box 2)
  - Zeleny, Charles (Box 2)
- Oversize materials
  - Conference on Genetics, Paleontology, and Evolution, NJ Jan. 1947 First Symposium for Growth and Development, Dinner of the American Zool. Society, Washington, D.C., 1939; 1924 (Folder OS-1)
  - Certificate - International Symposium of Nuclear Physiology and Differentiation Brazil, 1968 (Folder OS-2)
  - Photostat of a manuscript in German, 1906
  - AAAS, 1924 (Folder OS-3)